Long ago, Gold Roger,
the King of Pirates, obtained
everything the world had to offer,
and his dying roads drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it!
I left everything in one place.
Now you just have to find it!
And thus a new age began.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era!
Oh, I'm done playing
through with the waiting?
Either way, I'm feeling alive!
Look out below.
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
Raise your flag up high!
Hail a brand new dawn!
Blaze across the sky!
Time to journey on!
On your mark!
Camel of other things!
We're on Earth, a legendary!
If you can show your breath,
then we'll make some waves!
We run our daunted, ain't no beginners!
Cause if you're wanted,
then you're a winner!
For we are on the cruise,
and freedom is the only rule!
Fearless night and day,
cause that's just our way!
Find one piece, I'll be the first!
I'll put it, be so bad, so good first!
It's all this real!
It must be cause my hand's on a wheel!
I'm done playing, feel it's waiting!
In a world I'm feeling alive!
But I'll be loud!
Wake up, sunshine, here we go!
We have come so far!
Gotta make it to the end!
Whatever danger we find!
No one ever left behind!
I've always got your back, my friend!
Sail on shoreward, keep marching forward!
Dreaming from the very
first day I'd make my name!
And don't you know that
dream hasn't changed!
I'm done playing through with the wave!
In the world I'm feeling
alive, look out below!
Wake up, sunshine!
And here we go!
We go!
No!
You're staying right here!
Don't fight.
It's pointless.
Come on.
We're just wasting time. Yes, right.
If we don't hurry, they'll kill father.
I already told you, Jinbei!
Get out of my way so I can go
and kick this horny guy's ass!
And I told you to wait!
You aren't listening at all!
Let me finish speaking!
Now, how would you describe
the relationship between us?
We're friends!
That's right.
Although it is a simple matter for us,
our two peoples have been struggling to
establish such a
relationship for decades now.
I left you a message
saying not to fight Heart,
because I didn't want you
facing him recklessly.
Don't you see?
Think of how the fishman will view you.
If you rush in and show
aggression towards Carrot,
you'll be viewed as nothing more than just
another human bully oppressing our kind.
That is not what we want.
No, you should be a hero.
One that saves the island.
Hero?
Hell no! But why?
Obviously, because we're pirates! Come on!
Heroes are great, but I'm not one!
Seriously, do you even know
what you're asking me to do?
Let's say there's a chunk of meat, right?
Pirates will have a
banquet and dig right in,
but a hero would give it to other
people instead of eating it.
Screw that!
My meat is mine!
What a reason.
Luffy, I'll let you have
all the meat you want.
Just do as I say.
That's fair.
No way!
I'll make this simple.
There will come a time
when I need your help
so you'll rush in when
that moment arrives.
Okay.
Good.
But first, the plan.
We'll get caught on purpose.
To get us close afterwards while their
attention's on me then one of you pirates
will sneak out of megalo's
stomach and get yourself
into position to make
your attack did you see
a stomach the celestial
dragon's letter they have
it we need it hold on
what's this letter jimba?
Remember, Luffy was sleeping
through most of your story.
He doesn't know.
In short,
the letter is something Queen Otohime
acquired ten years ago at great personal risk.
It will define the very
future of this island.
They'll also have the key we'll need
to release the king from his bonds.
One of your crewmates must retrieve them.
Which one of you is up to the task?
I'm pretty good at stealing, but
still, I think I'll need Robin's help.
Of course.
Good.
Once you've managed to
free the king, get out.
I'll call Luffy and we'll take over.
After you emerge from Megalo's body,
the people of Fishman Island
will understand your intent.
Because they'll see you and I working
together against the common foe.
Princess, I must ask that you stay
somewhere safe outside the plaza.
It's for the best.
We'll pass the letter to you, whereupon
the entire royal family can escape.
During this time,
the rest of you will have to head to Ryugu
Palace to rescue your imprisoned friends.
Once they're free, get to the plaza
to back us up as soon as possible.
As for how you go about saving them, well,
that's for you to deal with. Come on!
Be specific!
Wow!
You can count on us big time!
After all, we've got the Sonny, right?
So no worries, we'll be there.
Once this is set in motion there's
no turning back we must succeed you
everyone here respects Jimbae whether
they're a civilian or outlaw they'll
follow after his example that's right
So if they see Jimbae working with
a human even a pirate they'll cheer
you on or maybe even fight beside you.
I mean, it's possible.
Strong hand.
Please, Luffy.
I'm only doing this
because you asked me to.
Got that? I made it.
Having people cheer for me? No thanks.
I don't like it.
I'm more for taking their
money and running away.
Speak for yourselves.
I'd go to the depths of hell if I knew the
mermaids would be there to cheer me on.
Very well, then.
Sounds like everything is settled, then.
All right, let's do this thing.
Wait.
Yeah, what's up? Something wrong?
What's our codename? Are
you kidding? Who cares?
We'll go already.
That's Skrya Luffy.
He's human and a pirate.
But on our side.
He showed up right when Princess
Shirahoshi called for him.
From the looks of things,
he's here to help Boss Team Bay
save the country from Horty's men.
Stop it!
Isn't it sweet how they cling to you?
But you've only delayed the
king's inevitable demise!
After all, you are nothing but a human!
Your beauty outshines
all others, princess!
Now that we've met, would you be
willing to show me your panties?
You can't ask her that!
Then show me yours!
No way in hell!
Okay, we're back!
Well done.
They're all ignoring you.
That's just because I was
using my inside voice.
Mommy Swan!
Now that I've saved those idiots from
the palace, you have to love me. Right?
Whatever.
Wait. He did what? Liar?
We got to the exit ourselves.
Maybe.
However, you never would have escaped
without me. That's a joke. Right, you guys?
Shirahoshi.
It's your mom's letter.
Here you go.
I can't tell you how
much this means to me.
I know it may look like an ordinary piece
of paper, but it's this island's hope.
That's enough, Whip Hachi.
It's not safe.
He's right.
You weren't meant to be
caught, so you must leave.
Now, while you can.
Wait, Luffy.
What did you call me?
Huh?
Just now, it was almost...
my name, but...
Yeah, I was wrong about you.
You're a wuss, but more
than just a crybaby.
So I'll call you Weepy Hachi.
It's an upgrade.
When a person feels as if
they've been wronged, well,
then it's only natural that
they would turn to hate.
That man.
Heart.
He's doing exactly that.
But you chose not to hate.
A coward wouldn't do that.
Hardship has only made
you stronger in the end.
Nami is right.
You endured.
Princess, I'm proud of you.
I appreciate the thought, but still,
I feel like I caused everyone trouble
by keeping this secret to myself.
I'm sorry.
You're mistaken.
You've done quite well.
Your intentions were pure, just
like those who have come before you.
You can't tell them
you have to hold it in.
Listen, don't become angry on my behalf!
I don't want that.
Our heroes planted a seed in your
heart and it has blossomed beautifully.
You have lived by their example.
Well, if everyone else
thought the way you do,
then there would be no
more fighting and the
conflict between fishmen
and humans would be?
over at last.
You may have suffered through those
past years alone, but that doesn't make
that time meaningless.
Single-handedly, you are a
defender, protecting the virtues of
others day after day.
But today, we're here.
We'll protect them for you.
I killed
so much!
You still cry, baby.
That's for sure.
Strahd!
Take him down!
I should have known Vander
Decken was going to fail me.
He couldn't even get rid
of one lousy princess.
Captain Heart!
Her power is too great.
It really is the stuff of legends.
Once I found out it was real I knew I had
to eliminate her as soon as possible. Sir.
But then, you got in my way.
Admittedly,
I should have known
something was wrong when
you were captured without
putting up a fight,
Jinbei.
You really like these humans, don't you?
People like you are the worst.
You've completely forgotten your pride.
See, you grew up with
Dock in our district.
And let's not forget Arlong.
He was like your brother.
Both of them were beaten
or killed by humans.
But instead of avenging them, you
wouldn't get in bed with the humans.
It's pathetic.
Jinbei, godless like Neptune.
But soon, everything is going to change.
Once I'm king, that is. Hear that?
I'll start with the world summit.
That'll be the perfect place.
With every ruler in the surface world
in one place, they'll be easy to kill.
Then the whole world will learn
to fear our underwater kingdom.
Their kingdoms in disarray
will drag the humans
into the depths and
enslave every last one.
In time, there won't be a
soul left to stand against us,
and we will rule the Great Pirate Era.
Oh yes, you pirates, we'll bow
the same as everybody else.
Just you wait. See?
These humans are more than capable of
holding their own, yet they kneel before me.
That's right.
In a moment you'll be just like them.
Straw Hats.
Is that so?
And to think there are only ten
of you here to stand in my way!
What can you possibly
do when we're 100,000?!
KILL THEM, NEW FISHMENT PIRATES!
Here they come!
No way we can fight this many at once!
We're done for!
This is exactly the reason I don't
like hanging out with you guys!
Before this begins, it's been a
pleasure traveling with all of you.
Don't say that!
There are so many enemies.
Wow, if I try to count them
all, my eyes may pop out.
And again, I don't have eyes.
So they can't!
Just 100,000?
That's nothing we can't handle, right?
Hey, wait!
You're just saying that because
you're hiding behind us!
And here I go!
It's time to shine!
Super Harbored Me! All right!
Let's do this already! Get over here!
In case you can't count,
we're each gonna have to take down
10,000 of these guys to win this fight.
They have numbers, but it
doesn't make them stronger.
I mean, it's not like they're
Navy Admirals or anything.
So don't crap yourself.
After these guys, you're next.
Number 10,001. Bring it on.
I can't wait.
Hey, Luffy.
Oh, no.
Those four million berries are mine.
Now they're mine.
It's too easy.
Kill him!
Ah!
What the hell just happened?
but he didn't do anything
and he still knocked them all
out hey get up guys come on
damn he took down half of us
in an instant that was 50 000
of our men what did he even
do did everyone see that yeah
but i don't know what it was
so much power for one so young
wait did the Straw Hat guy
really do that yeah too cool
that Haki that training paid
off i see unreal i mean
conqueror's Haki scary sure is
but i'd expect no less otherwise
he couldn't be my captain
Your name's Heart, right?
I'm about to kick your ass.
You want to become the king
of a country or whatever?
Fine, I don't care.
But king of the pirates? Nuh-uh.
That's my job.
It's true.
We may have lost 50,000.
But take heart.
We still have 50,000 left.
Those insufferable Straw Hat Pirates have
sought to shadow our dreams at every turn.
They must pay!
The traitor Jinbei is no better.
He follows in Otohime's footsteps
and befriends the humans.
But that is not the future
we fishmen wish to create!
He's right!
Straw Hat's a damn human!
What the hell does he
know about our people?
Anjibe!
If he wants to turn his back
on his brothers, kill him too!
Geez, you knocked out too many.
Leave some for me. Oh, yeah. My bad.
Hey, don't get ahead of yourself.
I'm taking 30,000.
Got it, lost head?
Shut up, dirty cook.
You're dead now!
Don't mess with us!
Okay!
Go third gear!
Just come at me!
I'll take all of you!
His arm is I know it's huge here goes.
Quick we had better assist him!
This is heaven for me I
won't let you destroy it.
Still don't want to give
up well more fun for
me I was thinking this
island is teeming with.
Invaluable archaeological resources the way
you're rampaging around and damaging it.
You ought to be ashamed look at
that crown they're ready to rock.
I'd say a 50,000-man brawl is the perfect
time to take them for a test drive.
Test drive?
Did you say them? Them who?
The Sonny just got two
brand-new weapons. Big ones.
Do you guys want to see them?
Yeah, of course we do!
You should keep an eye on your princess.
That's a pretty big target.
She's mine now!
The Water Shot!
They didn't need me after all.
Did you see that crap?
He deflected Captain Horty's water shot
with his own, like it was nothing at all!
I am so done with that big blue traitor!
He's as much trouble as
Straw Hats, maybe more!
Huh, that raw power of yours
is harnessed very poorly.
Your fishman karate needs work.
Wait a minute, I've heard
stories about this guy.
He was the first fishman
to join the Seven Warlords.
Yeah, and then after he resigned,
his bounty jumped up to
400 million berries, right?
This is hopeless.
We can't win against that guy.
Why don't you fools stop
chattering and start fighting?
If you intend to kill the princess, you'll
have to square with the rest of us first.
Go forward, Iron Shell Squad.
Three swords time.
Black Rope.
Shotsumaki!
Ah, he cut through their shells.
It's like they were made out of cheese.
What the hell?
They all drop like flies.
Is this guy the Grim Reaper or what?
It's not doing work.
This is sick.
It's a sword hurricane.
Ryan, you're gonna get cut.
How long is this thing gonna last?
...until you get to hell.
Why don't you idiots use your brains?
Inflate your bubbles!
Let's go!
Attack from the sky!
Kill Pichiro Hachi!
Watch out, we'll stab you!
Go, Harrison Bond!
It's the Sea Urchin Spike Unit!
And the leader, Harrison Bond!
Before you do anything else,
take out the kicking guy!
Harry...
Seth... Paul!
Well, what are you gonna do now, huh?
Sanji!
Do be careful!
How can you be so calm
at a time like this? Hey!
It's been a while since then.
I ran like hell.
Come back candy boy!
Over my dead body.
I brought my favorite dress just for you.
Why don't you try it all?
Don't be shy, it's just us.
That's not the problem, forget it.
Through the rain.
And the snow.
Through thunder and
lightning, I never stopped.
Cigar fires, you stubborn bastard!
Aren't you adorable?
You can't just run away
from us forever, you know?
One of these days, we're starting
to catch right up to you!
Oh, Sanji
I've gotten myself out of tougher
spots than this, haven't I?
Sanji!
My courage had left me and
there was nowhere to run.
Then...
What the? He's gone!
I found a new path.
And then before long I.
Was flying!
Skywalk?
Sanji can walk on air now,
like those other guys!
Skywalk. Oh, I see.
Not moonwalk.
Hey, scumbags!
Whoa!
He's flying!
If you've got something to say to the
princess, she'll have to go through me first.
Because I just happen to be her.
Knight in shining armor!
Thank you, Sanji.
Are you some kind of wise guy?
Let's cook these small fries.
Let's get this over with already!
Actually, I have a better idea!
How about instead, we leave the world's
most lovely mermaid princess alone, huh?!
Now here's some party music!
What's going on?
Why'd it get dark?
Welcome all to this festival night!
What the...
I guess, it was not a dream,
that big fight we were having.
Now, it's time to set up the fireworks!
I mean, this is much fun in years! Ha-ha!
It's beautiful!
Hey, what the hell are you guys aiming at?
Just kill her!
Yeah, but we can't.
We're enjoying the festival too much.
Cut.
Sorry, party's over.
Queen Tortillas, Fantasia.
Neal, move!
Gigantesco, mono!
Legs!
And stop!
Sorry!
There's a lot of screaming going on.
Is that good or bad?
It's way too cramped for
us all to be in here.
Then why don't you get out?
You're not even interested
in the weapons anyway.
Because if I go outside,
I'm going to have to fight.
I don't want to be stuck out there either.
Franky, can we hurry
this up a little, please?
I can't rush greatness, kid.
But fine, let's do this.
Actually, I'm getting
pretty excited now, too!
That's great, but can you move?
I'm supposed to operate this thing
It got bigger
Why couldn't it start out this way?
It's showtime!
There ain't nothin'
stoppin' this unveiling!
Wait, wait!
Yeah, but for what?
Let's rock and roll!
Get him swatted in there!
It doesn't matter how big
your legs or arms are,
cause you ain't gonna be nothin' but a
dead woman once we get our sneakers in ya!
Better than that case!
Soldier Dark Sister.
Channel 4.
Arch Black Rhino.
It's F R U 4.
A motorbike! So cool! I want it!
That's one tough machine!
And stylish too!
Let's see this venom of yours!
He's coming right at us!
You can try stinging it
if you really want to!
But this monster's made of pure steel!
How was that?
On a scale of one to super!
Someone stop that guy!
I got him!
Time for steel on steel!
Just leave it to me, boys!
Come on!
You're not scared, are you?
The new number, Shadow 5!
Brachiotek 5 is here!
No way!
A dinosaur!
You guys see that perfect shot I made?
Yeah, but I don't think you're
using this to its full potential.
Man, and here I thought
Brachio was just a shipwright.
Attention! Cock 2!
I'm Commander Chopper!
We have enemy bogeys
inbound off our 9 o 'clock!
Hey, you need a fight, too!
This is crazy.
I mean, they didn't look this tough.
There's only ten of them,
but they're taking on a hundred
thousand like it was nothing at all.
We're counting on you!
Get up, Timmy!
This has gone on too long.
Rise! My Kraken!
Whoa!
It's huge!
You have ten targets.
Kill the humans. Go!
Crush them! You heard me!
It doesn't matter how
strong the Straw Hats are,
they're all goners if they get
smashed by those giant tentacles.
Yeah, the Kraken always does
whatever Captain Ordy tells it to do.
And it's strong as hell!
They don't have a pair against
our deep-de-wrecking ball!
Oh, hey, it's that thing.
What are you waiting for?
Get to it!
Seeing as I'm the one who dragged you
here all the way from the North Pole,
that makes me your master.
So kill them already!
Or I kill you.
Please, can we talk about this?
Oh, hey, Tsutome!
Don't tell me you can't see me down here!
You were my pet for a while!
You and I are buddies!
We found him!
Luffy, no!
That's people!
Hey, knock it off, cinema!
Yeah!
Alrighty!
Let's get moving!
Ha ha ha ha!
Ah!
The dragon has betrayed us!
Dragon!
Knock it off!
You're the occupants!
Crusher! All right!
Captain, help me.
Go that way, buddy!
Dammit! What's going on?
It's doing everything Straw Hat says!
But why?
Listen up, Tsurume!
I want you to stay here
and protect Weepy Hachi!
I can't believe you managed to
ingratiate yourself to the Kraken.
It seems no matter where you go, you
always befriend the highest caliber allies.
Think so?
Um, thank you very much for
lending us your power, Sodom.
There's still a lot of these guys left.
All right, bring it on.